Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union Additional Photographs 5917 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Alpha Chemical Contract (Box 20, Folder 25)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 25; 1 photograph
- Alpha Chemical Scholarship - 3/1984 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 26; 1 photograph
- Alpha Distributing Contract - 3/1983 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 27; 3 photographs
- Alpha Distributing Corp. 1979 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 28; 3 photographs
- AMC and BW Convention - 7/1964 (1) (Box 20, Folder 29)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 29; 26 photographs
- AMC and BW Convention - 7/1964 (2) (Box 20, Folder 30)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 29; 12 photographs
- AMC and BW Convention, San Diego, 7/1968 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 30; 26 photographs
- AMC and BW Convention, Sam Drego, 7/1968 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 32; 17 photographs
- Amalgamated Convention, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 31; 24 photographs
- Amalgamated Convention, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 32; 11 photographs
- AMC & BW Civil Rights Conference, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 33; Letter no picture
- AMC & BW of NA Washington Conference - 6/1965 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 34; 3 photographs
- Amalgamated Officers (Box 20, Folder 37)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 35; 15 photographs
- APA Founding Conference - 1st Board Mtg. (Box 20, Folder 38)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 36; 17 photographs
- APA (Amalgamated Press Assoc.) 10/1974 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 37; 7 photographs
- APA - 6/1976 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 38; 8 photographs
- American Jewish Labor Council (Box 20, Folder 41)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 39; 2 photographs
- American Leather Contract - 4/1978 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 40; 5 photographs
- American Leather Fire - 1/1/1968 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 41; Empty----
- American Leather Party - 12/5/1983 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 42; 4 photographs
- Angel Reception - 3/16/1979 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 43; 16 photographs
- Angola Seminar, Meeting -- 2-3/76, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 44; 29 photographs
- Anti-Trapping Bill hearing - 8/5/1984 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 45; 1 photographs
- Antonovich ratification meeting - 3/24/1987 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 46; 2 photographs
- Glassman Meacham Archery Photos for Tempo (Box 20, Folder 49)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 47; 6 photographs
- Ray Arnett Reception - 7/15/1981 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 48; 7 photographs
- New ARO contract negotiations - 4/1983 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 51
- ARO PEA Meeting - 12/1977 (Box 20, Folder 52)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 49a; 1 photograph
- Jack Arra Farewell Testimonial - Jan. 23, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 49; 4 photographs
- Assoc. Fur Mfrs. Contract Signing - 3/9/1987 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 50; 1 photograph
- Auction Ratification Meetings & Committees - 1/1970 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 51; 10 photographs
- Auction Shops: Meeting - 11/2/1967 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 52
- Badillo visit to Webster - 3/1976 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 53; 4 photographs
- Mary Baker Music Group 6/1983 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 54; 4 photographs
- Banquet Speakers (1) (Box 21, Folder 7)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 55; 26 photographs
- Banquet Speakers (2) (Box 21, Folder 8)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 55; 22 photographs
- Banquets - Misc. (1) (Box 21, Folder 9)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 56; 26 photographs
- Banquets - Misc. (2) (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Banquets - Misc. (3) (Box 21, Folder 11)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 56; 25 photographs
- Baratta Testimonials - 1/7/1967 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 57; 1 photograph
- Barbaro Campaign 1981 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 58; 1 photograph
- Barbaro Park Dedication (Box 21, Folder 14)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 59; 2 photographs
- Bechroth Shop Meeting - Dec. 1970 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 60; 1 photograph
- John Bell - Subway Pix (Box 21, Folder 16)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 61; 2 photographs
- Belsky Bon Voyage - 3/1976 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 62; 6 photographs
- Benefit Fund Trustees - Contacts (Box 21, Folder 18)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 63; 1 photograph
- Alex Bethea (Box 21, Folder 19)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 64; 2 photographs
- Billante Dinner - 6/11/1973 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 65; 1 photograph
- Blood Bank (Box 21, Folder 21)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 66; 9 photographs
- Blood Bank - 6/24/1957 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 67; 1 photograph
- Blood Bank - Resina Automatic -- 12/2/1965 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 68; 8 photographs
- Blood Bank, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 69; 7 photographs
- Blood Bank - 4/30/1968 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 70; 4 photographs
- Blood Bank, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 71; 3 photographs
- Blood Bank - May 1970 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 72; 2 photographs
- Blood Bank April 1970 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 73; 2 photographs
- Blood Bank - April 1972 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 74; 6 photographs
- Blood Bank 1972 Morse (Box 21, Folder 30)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 75; 5 photographs
- Blood Bank - May 22, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 76; 6 photographs
- Blood Bank - Morse - Oct. 1973 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 77; 3 photographs
- Blood Bank - April 8, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 78; 7 photographs
- FLM - Blood Bank -- 4/8/1974 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 79; 6 photographs
- Blood Bank - April 1976 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 80; 3 photographs
- Blood Bank - 10/20/1977 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 81; 4 photographs
- Blood Bank - 10/20/1977 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 82; 1 photograph
- Blood Bank - 6/11/1979 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 83; 7 photographs
- Blood Bank - 5/18/1982 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 84; 13 photographs
- Blood Bank 5/1983 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 85; 4 photographs
- Blum & Fink Workers (Box 21, Folder 41)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 86; 2 photographs
- Board Room Decorations (Box 21, Folder 42)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 87; 2 photographs
- Borden - Lyons Xmas Party - 12/1979 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 88; 5 photographs
- Borden - Lyons Christmas Party - 12/27/1980 - Rountawner, Newark, NY (Box 21, Folder 44)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 89; 9 photographs
- Borden - Lyons Clambake - 8/23/1975 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 90; 4 photographs
- Borden - Lyons - Cong - Horton - 9/1974 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 91; 5 photographs
- Borden - Lyons Picnic - Aug. 1974 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 92; 5 photographs
- Borden - Lyons Settlement - 2/1978 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 93; 4 photographs
- Wellsboro - Negotiating Comm. (Box 21, Folder 49)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 94
- Borden - Wellsboro Negotiations - Dec. 1980 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 95; 1 photograph
- Borden-Wellsboro Negotiations - Feb. 1984 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 96; 2 photographs
- Borden-Wellsboro Nominating Meeting 4/18/1984 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 97
- Borden-Wellsboro Ratification Mtg. 12/31/1980 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 98; 3 photographs
- Borden-Wellsboro Re enrollment Oct. 1983 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 99; 2 photographs
- Borden's - FLM at work (Wellsboro) (Box 22, Folder 5)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 100; EMPTY
- Bowling, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 101; 14 photographs
- Bowling Match - Hollander Middletown (Box 22, Folder 7)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 102; 4 photographs
- Brier and Harris (Box 22, Folder 8)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 103; 3 photographs
- Morris Brier Retirement Party 10/1/1976 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 104; 2 photographs
- Brotherhood Festival Feb. 15, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 105; 15 photographs
- Bucilla Class and Publication 1977 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 106; 2 photographs
- Building Bulletins (Box 22, Folder 12)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 107
- Sam Burt (Duplicates) (Box 22, Folder 13)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 108; 14 photographs
- Sam Burt Campaign for Congress (Box 22, Folder 14)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 109; 6 photographs
- Sam Burt Dinner May 4, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 110; 13 photographs
- Sam Burt Houses - Dedication 6/14/1967 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 111; 4 photographs
- Sam Burt Houses Day - Proclamation 1965 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 112; 2 photographs
- Sam Burt Manager Furriers Joint Board (Box 22, Folder 18)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 113; 5 photographs
- Sam Burt Memorial Meeting Sept. 1961 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 114; 10 photographs
- Sam Burt Report on European Trip Oct. 1960 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 115; 5 photographs
- Butchers Dietrich Council Mar. 20, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 116; 1 photograph
- Canada Fur Institute - Edmonton - Jan. '85, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 117; 4 photographs
- Canada Fur Meeting 9/1979 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 118; 1 photograph
- Candidates' Meeting 10/24/1977 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 119; 15 photographs
- Carabanchel 10 Press Conference - Madrid Dec. 1973 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 120; 1 photograph
- Carabanchel Report Meeting 1/8/1974 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 121; 3 photographs
- Clarence Carr - Gloversville (Box 22, Folder 27)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 122; 1 photograph
- Central American Delegation 10/28/1985 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 123; 7 photographs
- Central Labor Council Dinner 2/1972 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 124; 2 photographs
- CGTU Meeting 12/3/1982 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 125
- Checks (Box 22, Folder 31)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 126; 12 photographs
- Chestnut Operating Class 3/1978 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 127; 1 photograph
- Chestnut Operating Contract 12/1978 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 128; 3 photographs
- Chestnut Operating Meeting 10/1977 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 129; 1 photograph
- Chestnut Operating Meeting 8/16/1982 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 130; 2 photographs
- Chestnut Operating Negotiations Dec. 1984 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 131; 6 photographs
- Chestnut Operating Shop Meeting 9/4/1975 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 132; 2 photographs
- Chicago Trip - Locals 2.3, FLM Feb. 1971 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 133; 2 photographs
- Children's Christmas Parties (Box 22, Folder 39)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 134; 21 photographs
- Chanukah Children's Party (1) (Box 22, Folder 40)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 135; 26 photographs
- Chanukah Children's Party (2) (Box 22, Folder 41)
- Chanukah Children's Party (3) (Box 22, Folder 42)
- Chanukah Children's Party (4) (Box 22, Folder 43)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 135; 20 photographs
- Chanukah Christmas Children's Party (1) (Box 23, Folder 1)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 136; 26 photographs
- Chanukah Christmas Children's Party (2) (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Chanukah Christmas Children's Party (3) (Box 23, Folder 3)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 136; 16 photographs
- Chanukah Christmas Children's Party (1) (Box 23, Folder 4)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 137; 26 photographs
- Chanukah Christmas Children's Party (2) (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Chanukah Christmas Children's Party (3) (Box 23, Folder 6)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 137; 5 photographs
- Children's Christmas Party (Box 23, Folder 7)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 138; 13 photographs
- Children's Christmas Party (Box 23, Folder 8)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 139; 24 photographs
- Children's Christmas Party (Box 23, Folder 9)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 140; 9 photographs
- Children's Christmas Parties - Joint Board Council (Box 23, Folder 10)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 141; 21 photographs
- Children's Christmas Party (Box 23, Folder 11)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 142; 4 photographs
- Children's Christmas Party, 1949 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 143; 11 photographs
- Children's Christmas Party, 1950 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 144; 16 photographs
- Children's Christmas Party Dec. 15, 1951 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 145; 16 photographs
- Children's Christmas Party, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 146; 12 photographs
- Jt. Bd. Children's Christmas Party Dec. 18, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  collection re-organized this was box 17, ff 147; 9 photographs
- Children's Christmas Party Dec. 10, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 1; 8 photographs
- Jt. Bd. Children's Christmas Party Dec. 1956 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 2; 12 photographs
- Children's Xmas Party (Box 24, Folder 3)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 3; 6 photographs
- Children's Christmas Party (Box 24, Folder 4)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 4; 8 photographs
- Children's Christmas Party (Box 24, Folder 5)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 5; 8 photographs
- Children's Christmas Party - Dec. 1961 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 6; 7 photographs
- Children's Christmas Party - Dec. 1962 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 7; 2 photographs
- Children's Christmas Party - Dec. 15, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 8; 11 photographs
- Children's Christmas Party (Box 24, Folder 9)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 9; 16 photographs
- Local 48 Children's Christmas Party Dec. 1964 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 10; 10 photographs
- Children's Christmas Party 12/12/1964 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 11; 21 photographs
- Children's Christmas Party - Easton, Pa. Dec. 1967 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 12; 10 photographs
- Children's Christmas Parties, N.Y., Newark 12/1967 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 13; 10 photographs
- Children's Christmas Party Dec. 21, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 14; 20 photographs
- Children's Dental Health Day 4/25/1981 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 15; 13 photographs
- Children's Dental Health Day 4/25/1981 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 16
- Children's Dental Health Day - Parson, WV 10/11/1981 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 17; 12 photographs
- Children's Dental Health Programs (Box 24, Folder 18)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 18; 28 photographs
- Children's Health Day - LICH 12/7/1985 (1) (Box 24, Folder 19)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 19; 26 photographs
- Children's Health Day - LICH 12/7/1985 (2) (Box 24, Folder 20)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 19; 14 photographs
- Children's Health Day - Passaic Gen. Hosp. 12/14/1985 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 20; 18 photographs
- Children's Health Day - Raffle Winners (Box 24, Folder 22)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 21; 2 photographs
- Chile Demonstration June 1977 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 22; 5 photographs
- Christmas Party, Executive Boards - Dec. 1967 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 23; 22 photographs
- FLM Xmas Party 12/14/1981 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 24; 11 photographs
- Christmas Party - Newark 12/1979 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 25; 11 photographs
- Christmas Party - N.Y. 12/1979 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 26; 14 photographs
- Christmas Party - NY Div. Bds. 12/1980 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 27; 3 photographs
- Citibank Picket Line 6/1977 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 28; 1 photograph
- City Council Members at Joint Board Meeting (Box 24, Folder 30)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 29; 3 photographs
- Civilian Review Board 11/2/1966 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 30; 15 photographs
- CLA Contract Signing 9/1977 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 31; 1 photograph
- CLA Shop Meetings - June - Oct. 1976 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 32; 5 photographs
- Cleaning Section (Box 24, Folder 34)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 33; 2 photographs
- Cleaning Section Contract, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 34; 10 photographs
- Cleaning Section Contract Signing - 7/1953 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 35; 3 photographs
- Cleaning Section Meeting 5/30/1973 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 36; 1 photograph
- Dr. Charles Clements - El Salvador Meeting 5/31/1983 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 37; 1 photograph
- Coalition of Black Trade Unionists - Detroit 5/3-5/5, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 38; EMPTY
- CBTU Dinner (Box 24, Folder 40)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 39; 4 photographs
- Joe Cohn Dinner (Box 24, Folder 41)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 40; EMPTY
- John Coker (Box 24, Folder 42)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 41; 9 photographs
- Community Services Committee - AFL-CIO Institute (Box 25, Folder 1)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 42; 22 photographs
- Community Services Committee Meetings (Box 25, Folder 2)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 43; 3 photographs
- Community Services Committee Party (Box 25, Folder 3)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 44; 32 photographs
- Community Services Committee Party - June 1967 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 45; 28 photographs
- Community Services Forum on Medicaid (Box 25, Folder 5)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 46; 8 photographs
- Community Services Forum - Rents and Housing Oct. 1963 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 47; 2 photographs
- Community Services AFL-CIO Council (Box 25, Folder 7)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 48; 5 photographs
- Constitutional Convention (CON CON) 11/31/1967 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 49; 7 photographs
- Contacts - Misc. (1) and Photos (Box 25, Folder 9)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 50; 2 photographs
- Contacts - Misc. (2) (Box 25, Folder 10)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 50
- Contacts - Misc. (3) and Photos (Box 25, Folder 11)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 50; 1 photograph
- Contacts - Misc. (1) (Box 25, Folder 12)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 51
- Contacts - Misc. (2) (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Contemporary Displays Contract 5/1983 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 52; 1 photograph
- Contributions (Box 25, Folder 15)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 53; 4 photographs
- Conventions and Conferences (Box 25, Folder 16)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 54; 19 photographs
- John Conyers, Jr. (Nat'l. Coalition to Fight - Inflation and Unempl.) -- Luncheon -- 5/15/1977 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 55; 6 photographs
- Co-Op City Rally - March 7, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 56; 4 photographs
- Irwin Corey - Split personality (Box 25, Folder 19)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 57; 1 photograph
- Irwin Corey (Box 25, Folder 20)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 58; 2 photographs
- CRA Blood Bank (Box 25, Folder 21)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 59; 1 photograph
- CRA Blood Bank (Box 25, Folder 22)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 60; 6 photographs
- CRA Closing (Box 25, Folder 23)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 61 photographs
- CRA - Morse - Meisel Contax - 1/28/1971 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 62; 2 photographs
- CRA Pension Meetings 11-12/1982 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 63; 7 photographs
- Credit Union Committee, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 64; 1 photograph
- Crown - Monarch (Box 25, Folder 27)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 65; 6 photographs